UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials
1997-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 10
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/050 AV
2.67 cubic feet
2.7 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7101460
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 02, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/050: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050 MB: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/050 PUBS: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024: UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 PUBS: UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Organizaiton; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 10 (New York, N.Y.); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7101460
- UNITE for the future, 1 (Box 1)
- Tribute and Remembrance: Asian Americans after 9/11, 2 (Box 1)
- UNITE for the future, 3 (Box 1)
- Made in the USA, 1998; 4 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  20/20 Friday, March 13, 1998
- UNITE! Members love New York, 5 (Box 1)
- Local 23-25 UNITE, 6 (Box 1)
- Global Fairness Lobby Day 4/4/2000, 7 (Box 1)
- The Rise of Women and Minorities: the New American Labor Movement, 8 (Box 1)
- The Rise of Women and Minorities: the New American Labor Movement, 9 (Box 1)
- From Beijing with love, 10 (Box 1)
- Unite New Members, 11 (Box 1)
  English, Spanish
- Frontline: Is Wal-Mart Good for America?, 12 (Box 1)
- UNITE! Convention 2003, 13 (Box 1)
  Spanish version
- UNITE! Convention 2003, 14 (Box 1)
  Spanish Version
- Unlabeled, 15 (Box 1)
- UNITE: 2003 UNITE! Convention, 16 (Box 1)
- UNITE Campaign for the future, 17 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 18 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 19 (Box 1)
- The Las Vegas Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Coalition, 20 (Box 1)
- Anastasia Ordonez: Behind the Label.org, 2001; 21 (Box 1)
  9/21/2001
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 22 (Box 1)
  English/Spanish version
- Proudly made in NY, 23 (Box 1)
- Mandela w/o states, 24 (Box 1)
- Unite New Members, 25 (Box 1)
- Label has Chinese symbols on it, 26 (Box 1)
  MASTER
- Bessie Cohen: World Today CNN, 1999; 27 (Box 1)
  Feb 24, 1999
- A day's work a day's pay, 28 (Box 1)
- UNITE! Members love New York, 29 (Box 1)
- Kopeyia Ghana School Fund, Inc., 30 (Box 1)
- Union Voice 9/2003, 31 (Box 1)
  Mobilizing for the 1WFR w/Lana Chevrg
- Stop Au Sida, Stop AIDS, Alto Al Sida (Box 2)
- Unlabeled (Box 3)
- Les Miserable #2 (Box 4)
- Local 23-25, UNITE, Executive Board Meeting, Thursday, August 14, 1997 (Box 5)
- FAST Track (Box 6)
- 5/24/1997 Alice -- New Members (Box 7)
- GTL 1 (8/28) (Box 8)
- 3/10, Local 23-25 Election (Box 9)
- Unlabeled (Box 10)
- Margaret Chin (Box 11)
- Unlabeled (Box 12)
- Civil Rights Radio Broadcast - Sept. 2001 (Box 13)
- Unlabeled (Box 14)
- Unlabeled (Box 15)